beeinspiredclothing.com 2019-01-24

# Privacy Policy – Bee Inspired Clothing

Bee Inspired Clothing LTD Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.beeinspiredclothing.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

\- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

Communicate with you;

Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and

We also share this information with our couriers, DPD, DHL, AFS, Royal Mail and Global-e.

MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS

At Bee Inspired Clothing we want to optimise the customer experience, we therefore use personal data for marketing purpose. This may include postal mail, SMS and emails to update you on the latest offers and events. We may also show you content via social media platforms and other external applications such as Facebook, Instagram and Google advertising.

You have the right to opt out of receiving promotional communications at any time, by:

  1. informing us that you wish to change your marketing preferences by contacting our customer support team at [support@beeinspiredclothing.com](mailto:support@beeinspiredclothing.com);

  2. making use of the simple “unsubscribe” link in emails or the “STOP” number for texts;

This may not stop service messages such as order updates.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).  

In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you. General information on Klarna you can find here. Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in Klarna’s privacy policy: <http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy>

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: [ https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at[ http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work).

This site uses the following third party cookies for marketing, you can read their policies:

Facebook:[ https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/)

Google Analytics & Tag Manager:[ https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies)

Instagram:[ https://www.instagram.com/legal/cookies/](https://www.instagram.com/legal/cookies/)

Twitter:[ https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies)

Criteo:[ https://www.criteo.com/privacy/](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/)

Adroll: <https://app.adroll.com/optout/safari>[ ](https://app.adroll.com/optout/safari)

Sale Cycle: <http://www.salecycle.com/service-privacy-notice/>

You can adjust your setting to block cookies from specific websites, below is a list of the most used browsers by our customers, please note if you choose to block our cookies this website might not work as efficiently.

Apple Safari:[ https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411?locale=en_US](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411?locale=en_US)

Google Chrome:[ https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en)

Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>

Mozilla Firefox: [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies)

Microsoft Edge: <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy>

Opera: <https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/>

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [support@beeinspiredclothing.com](mailto:support@beeinspiredclothing.com) or by mail using the details provided below:

211 MacLellan Street, Glasgow G41 1RR, United Kingdom
